Guide to the Preservation Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Preservation department records [computer files], 2004-2013; Accession 2014-A-033
  Restricted until January 1, 2048
  - Committees
  - Department meetings
  - Preservation renovation
  - Renovation
  - Security survey documents
- Preservation Department records, 1951-2015; Accession 2016-A-024
  Restricted until January 1, 2050
  - Action Planning, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Action Planning Folder 1 of 2, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Action Plan Report Folder 2 of 2, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Action Plan, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Action Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acquisitions, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Committee on Art Conservation, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, Preservation, 1972-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, Tech Services FY 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, Tech Services FY 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, Preservation
    - 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - RAMP - Impact Group (DW Files), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Presentation - "The Next 5 Years" 2008-2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report 2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Annual Association Research Libraries (ARL) Preservation Statistics Analysis, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ARL - Annual Statistics 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ARL - Annual Statistics 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ARL - Annual Statistics 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Automation Plan (Paul) 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Backlog (Preservation Dept) 1990, 1990 March (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Backlog (Preservation Dept) 1990, 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Binding, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Binding Management-NNC, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Binding Paper (Gay Walker), 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Binding Contracts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Binding Policies - Background, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Binding Automation, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Binding Policy Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Binding Policy Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Binding Study (RFP), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Binding Workshops - Yale, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Binding Workshops - Extra Handouts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Preservation Brochure, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Budget Reduction Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Care and Handling Workshop, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cataloging - 583 Fields, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Circulation Dept Issues, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Circulation Memos, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Collections Care Program (CCP), 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CCP - Historical (Various), 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Collections Care Unit - Establishment Budget, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Collections Care Program / Space Re-organization, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Collections Care Program / Reorganization, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Collections Care Program / Job Descriptions, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlet Binding, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Collection Care Program / Shrink Wrap, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Collections Care Program / Bookplates, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Collections Care Program / Treatment Selection Guidelines, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Collection Care Manual, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Interns: UT-Austin Program and Mellon, 1994, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Collections Conservation - New England Training, 1992, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CT State Historical Records Advisory Board, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Conservation 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (Conway, Paul), 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence and Planning (Conway, Paul) Folder 1 of 2 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and Planning (Conway, Paul) Folder 2 of 2 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (Conway, Paul) / Core Preservation - Memos, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (Conway, Paul) D-Lib Magazine Article, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (Conway, Paul) Facilities Planning 1993, 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Conway, Paul (Linda Peterson) 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence / Memoranda (Watt, Marcia) 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: (Walker, Gay) 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (Watt, Marcia) 1987-90, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (Watt, Marcia) NYPL 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Corresondence (Watt, Marcia) 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Crosstraining, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dataloggers 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Disaster Flood Manual - YUL 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Mudd - Mold Problem 1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Disaster Workshop 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Discard Policy, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Divinity Preservation and Access (Luce Foundation), 1992 November (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Divinity School Day Missions Microfilm (NEH) 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Environment / HVAC / Air conditioning Sterling 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Environmental Controls 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Environmental Survey 1982, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Environmental Conditions (Stacks), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Art and Architecture Library 1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Environmental survey, Cross-Campus, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Drama, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Engineering, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Kline Science, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Forestry, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Geology, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Law, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Map / Atlas, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Math, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - MIA, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Microtext Reading Room, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Middle East Collection, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Pres Dept - Microform RR conditions, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Music, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Periodical Reading Room, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Preservation Costs, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Beinecke Condition Survey - N. Schrock, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Environmental Conditions (NEH) 1985 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Historic Sound Recordings (Environment) Collin Survey 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Environmental Standards NISO 1985-1993 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Exhibit - Preservation (Labels) 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit - Preservation (Labels), 1996 November (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Garland Reprint Project 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - General Bookbinding, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Generic Job Descriptions, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Grant Planning, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Guide to Preservation in Acquisitions Processing, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Historic Sound Recording - Move, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ideal Future, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Inter-library Loan, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - IPI - Image Permanence Institute - PEM (NEH Grant), 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - JSTOR, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Judaica Preservation Project, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kline Science Libraries, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - La Guardia Collaborative Imaging 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - La Guardia 8 / 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Leave Policy, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Preservation - Pres Div(ision) Lib Principal Priorities 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pres Dept - Mass Deacid PH Test 1999; samples sent to IPCH 2015, 1999-2015 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Pres-Mass Deacidification, Battelle 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Medieval Studies, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Pres - Microforms 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Microform NRMM (National Register of Microfilm Masters) 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Microform policy at Yale 1978-1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Microfiche 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm General Information, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm - Harvard - Quality Control of, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Natl. Underground Storage 1983-1987, 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm National Underground Storage 1988, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Pres - Microfilming Price List 1988, 0 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm / Film Costs - Comparison 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Microfilming Projects 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Microfilming - Bibliographic Issues 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Dissertation Microfilming Project 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Pres Dept - Microfilming Order Forms / 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Pres Dept - Microfilming Unit 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Microfilming Unit / Bi-weekly Meetings 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm MIcroMedia 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm MAPS (Micrographic Preservation Service) 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm MAPS 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm MSC Contract - Microfilming 1989 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Labels 1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Master Neg. Storage 1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm Price Lists 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Microfilming - Providence Group 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Microfilming Targets, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Microfilming Time Study, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm (Watt, Marcia) 1990 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Microwaving Books 1989, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Mudd Library 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - NEDCC Leaflet 1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - NEDCC Workshop - Denver, 1994 October (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - NEDCC - School for Scanning, 1995 April (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - School for Scanning Conference, 1995 March (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Needs Assessment 1991 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Needs Assessment / Sample Condition Surveys 1980-1993 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Netscape 1995 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - YUL Netware 1995 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - New Haven Registrar Project 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - New Haven - Vital Records Grant 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Nota Bene 1993 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - NOTIS P.I.G. 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - OCLC 1992 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - OCLC 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Orbis 1988 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Orbis 1988-1992 Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Orbis 1988-1992 Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Orbis 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Orbis Authorities 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Orbis Circulation 1991 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Orbis / GEAC Conversion 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Orbis - RLIN - QD 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Orbis Training Documents 1989 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Orbis Coordinating Group (OCG) 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Pres Dept Orientation Task 1991 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - YUL Org Charts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Paperback Binding Policy - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Topics - ALA - PADG and Queuing 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photo Preservation 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - PMT 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - PMT Notes 1994-1996, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - PMT 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - PMT 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Preservation N.S. 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Department 1980-1985, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Preservation Department 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Preserration Department 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Preservation Department 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Preservation Department Manual 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Preservation Department Procedures Manual 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Preservation Dept. Memos FY 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Preservation Dept. Program Development 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Preservation Dept. Manual Revision 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tech Services "Re Org I" 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Tech Services "Re Org II" 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Preservation Dept. Reorganization Folder 1 of 3, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Preservation Dept. Reorganization Folder 2 of 3, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Preservation Dept. Reorganization Folder 3 of 3, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Preservation Dept. Reorganization 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Preservation Department Quarterly Meetings 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Preservation Dept. - Staff Meetings 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Preservation/Circulation Meeting (Pres. Dept. Staff Meeting), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Preservation Dept. - Tech Svcs Mgmt Group (TSMG) 1993-1995 Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Preservation Dept. - Tech Svcs Mgmt Group (TSMG) 1993-1995 Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Preservation Dept. TSMG Agenda Items 1995 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Preservation Dept. Web-site Development 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Preservation ILL Task Force, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Preservation Planning (Short-term) 1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Pres. Planning Task Force - Meetings 1986 Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Pres. Planning Task Force - Meetings 1986 Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pres. Planning Task Force - Follow-up 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Pres. Planning Task Force Support Docs., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Collection Strength Preservation Survey (PPT Interviews) 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force Minutes 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force Final Report Folder 1 of 2 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force Final Report May 1986 Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force Final Report 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pres. Palnning Task Force: Objectives 1 Set, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pres. Planning Task Force: Objectives - Cost, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Preservation Planning Documents 1996 / (Action Plan), 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Planning Task Force; Objective 1: Air Conditioning 1986, 1986 - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - PPTF Objective 2: Preservation Backlog, 1986 - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - PPTF Objective 3: Refurbishing, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - PPTF Objective 4: Conservation Staff Increase, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - PPTF Objective 5: Reformatting Projects, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - PPTF Objective 7: Revise Cir. Rules, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - PPTF Objective 10: Archival Repairs / Housing, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - PPTF Objective 12: Monitor New Tech's, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - PPTF Objective 13: P.R., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Policy and Research Committee, Survey of Time Estimates for S.C.P. ("Simple Conservation Procedures"), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pres. Science Council (CPA), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Preservation Program Model 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Preservation Projects - Development 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Promotion Review Committee 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Publicity - Preservation 1985-86, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rainbow Reports (Pres. Dept. Finance) 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rainbow Reports (Pres. Dept. Finance) 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - RECON (Retrospective Conversion) Coordinating Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Preservation Reference Collection 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Preservation Resources (Web) 1995, 0 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Preservation - RLG (Research Lib Group), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Serials Preservation 1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Process Improvement - Technical Svcs - Meeting 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Treatment Solution / Triage 1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Renovation - SML 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Pres. Dept. - SML Renovation 1994 / Exhibit Space (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Pres. Dept. - SML Renovation - Exhibit, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Pres. Dept. - Renovation Sterling / Stacks 1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Renovation - SML 1995, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Renovation - Sterling - 1995, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Renovation / Room 3 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - SML Renovation Task Force 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - SML Renovation Collection Damage 1996 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Retrospective Conversion Projects 1993 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - RECON (Retrospective Conversion) 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Research Libraries Group (RLG) 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Serials Forum 1994 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Pres. Dept. Space Planning 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Preservation Space Planning 1991 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Space Planning 1993 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Space Planning 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Space Planning / Office of Facilities 1993 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Space Planning Task Force 1993 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Space Planning Task Force 1994 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Space Planning 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Space Planning Working Group / Off-campus Shelving 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Space Plannning: Off-site Shelving 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Space Planning (Library) Task Force 1993 Folder 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Space Planning (Library) Task Force 1993 Folder 2 of 2, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Space Planning: Rooms 5, 6 and 53, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Staff Recognition, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Standard MARC / Headings Task Group (Cataloging) 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - YUL - Strategic Plan and goals, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Technical Services 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - U.N. Scholar Workstation Task Force (Mellon Proposal) 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - USMARC 583 Field 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Video Archives 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Video (Interactive Video), Circa 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Videotape Preservation - Fortunoff 1989-1992, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Web Catalogue 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Web / YUL (Home) Page 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Workstations (Preservation) 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Workstation News 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Workstations Support 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - WWW Pages (Misc) 1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - WWW Publishing 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Yale Computer Center (Training) 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Yale Computer Center (Training) 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Yale Daily News Digital (Conversion) Project 2006-2013 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Yale Library Model 1986-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Yale Withdrawal (Library Materials) Policy 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Houghton Mifflin [Riverside Press Brass Dies] 1973, 1973-2007 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Riverside Press - Diestamps 2007 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, British Library 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Corresondence, Library of Congress 1973-1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence Newberry 1973-1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence Northeast Document Conversation Ctr., 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence NYPL 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence Horton, Carolyn 1974-1978, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence Kyle, Hedi (NY Botanical Garden) 1983, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence Lada-Mocarski, Polly 1977 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence / Lippincott, Gordon 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence / Roger Powell 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence / Silverman, Randy 1987 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Conservation Studio-General
    - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - 1970-1985 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 1990-2006 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Corresp / Consv Studio - Climate Control, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Corresp / Consv Studio - Endowments, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Corresp. / Conservation / Paper / Howell, Douglas 1974, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Consv Studio / Flood Manual Masters, 1983-2001 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Consv Studio / Flood Workshops, 1983-2000 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Consv Studio / Flood Response Info Medical Lib, Circa 1984 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Consv Studio - Flood Plan, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Consv - Pest Monitoring (Bugs at BRBL), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Consv Studio - Pest Monitoring (Beinecke), 1986-1996 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Consv Lab - Pest Monitoring - Beinecke, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Consv Studio / Power Post Beetles and related activities, 1976-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Consv Studio / Powder Post Beetles - Related Publications, 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Audio Visual Materials, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape show and Pamphlets Form Letters, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Consv Studio - Preservation Pamphlets; Inquiries, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Shows, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Consv Studio - Slide Tape show purchase/rent, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show purchase/rent, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show purchase/rent, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show purchase/rent, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show Purchase - Rental, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1987-1988 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1988-1989 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1989-1990 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1990-1991 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1991-1992 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1992-1993 Purchased, 1992-93 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1993-1994 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Consv Studio - Slide/Tape Show 1995-1997 Purchased (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1988-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Conservation Studio - Newspaper Articles, etc., 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bindery Equipment Ten Year Report, 1974-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hist of Consv - Mellon Foundation 1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Consv Studio - Paper Laboratory Design Peter Zegers, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Constu - Renovation 1998, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cons Studio - SML Refurbishing NEH, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Cons Studio - Best Practices - Mold Remediation, None (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Equipment Inventory, 1973-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cons Equipment Inventory 1992, 1983-1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cons Studio Costs 1973-1978, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cons Studio Interns 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Conservation Studio, Practicums and Internships 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cons Studio Intern, Susan Herion, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cons Studio Internship, Meg Brown, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Cons Studio Intern, Waechter, Wolfgang, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cons Studio Intern, Joan ten Hoor, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Cons Studio Intern, Stauderman, Sarah D., 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cons Studio Intern, Arthur Saxon, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Cons Studio Budget 1982, 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Catalog: Continuation Committee Report, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Care and Handling Guidelines 1982, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Conservation Studio 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Conservation Division Oreintation 1982 (Box 7, Folder 44)